http://www.leasebynet.com/privacy-policy.html

HomeAbout UsToyota Land CruiserLease SpecialsLinksLeasing FAQsUsed CarsSwap LeaseContact Us
Privacy Policy
Security & Privacy
Please read this Terms of Use and Privacy Agreement carefully before using LeaseByNet.com website. Your use of the Website is subject to your acceptance of this Agreement.
User Information and Privacy
We have created this Terms of Usage and Privacy Statement to help show LeaseByNet.com's commitment to privacy. This Statement describes LeaseByNet.com's information gathering and dissemination practices for the Website.
We do not automatically collect any personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, or email address, unless you voluntarily submit it. If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, we may collect them into a file specific to you. If, at any time, you do not wish to receive email from us, please send a message to info@leasebynet.com requesting that we stop.
We do use cookies to track non-personal information about our Website users such as the URL that the user has come from and goes to next, the Internet browser and type of operating system used, the user's location, and the user's IP address. We use IP addresses for system administration purposes so we can better understand which parts of our Website users visit most. Many sites automatically collect this information. We may use this information for such purposes as improving the content of our Website, marketing, advertising or research.
We do reserve the right to release current or past user information internally within LeaseByNet.com and its affiliates, partners and subsidiaries. We also reserve the right to release current or past user information to third parties for limited purposes if we believe that usage is (i) in violation of this Agreement; (ii) used to commit unlawful acts; and/or (iii) is required to be disclosed to comply with applicable laws or regulations, or with a court or administrative order. Except as stated in this paragraph, we will not share information specific to users with third parties. We may, however, disclose aggregate user information to third parties.
Data Security
LeaseByNet.com uses a secured network to store your personal information. In order to view or change personal information that has already been stored, a secured server is used and information is transmitted via SSL encryption.
Transactional Information
We make every effort to ensure that your purchase experience at LeaseByNet.com is secure. We use state-of-the-art data encryption technology to protect against loss, misuse or alteration of your user information. Secure Socket Layers (SSL) encrypt the
information sent between your computer and our database. In addition, we use Internet fraud screening to protect credit card transactions.
To be sure you're browsing secure pages, check your Web browser's status bar (located at the bottom of the window) for the closed padlock icon. This icon appears in the latest versions of Internet Explorer and Netscape Navigator to tell you that you are viewing a secure web page. Also, all browsers display an "s" after the "http" (https://.) in the Web site address to indicate that you're in a secure environment.
CONTACT INFORMATION
First Name:*
Last Name:*
State:*
Select
Alabama
Alaska
Arizona
Model:
Body Style:
Options:
Home | About Us | Swap Lease | Contact Us | Privacy Policy | Used Car
